[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Washington"]}, "docId": "130412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 31, "question": "What would you be doing right now, if you were in that job now?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "you", "be", "doing", "right", "now", ",", "if", "you", "were", "in", "that", "job", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "RB", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 32, "answer": "If I was in that job now, I would probably be sitting in Washington waiting for the current crisis to pass.", "answer_tokens": ["If", "I", "was", "in", "that", "job", "now", ",", "I", "would", "probably", "be", "sitting", "in", "Washington", "waiting", "for", "the", "current", "crisis", "to", "pass", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", ",", "NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "NN", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 40, "question": "Or is there, as some people, a chance that this could be more serious?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "is", "there", ",", "as", "some", "people", ",", "a", "chance", "that", "this", "could", "be", "more", "serious", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "EX", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "DT", "MD", "VB", "RBR", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 41, "answer": "I think it sounds kind of similar, piers, but I think there is something different this time.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "sounds", "kind", "of", "similar", ",", "piers", ",", "but", "I", "think", "there", "is", "something", "different", "this", "time", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Korea"]}, "docId": "130412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "TO", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBZ", "DT", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 54, "question": "What is the significance of that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "significance", "of", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 55, "answer": "Well, the amazing thing about north Korea is that it takes totalitarianism to an entirely new level, and besides all the control and the repression, there's a classification system that is superimposed on the entire society.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "amazing", "thing", "about", "north", "Korea", "is", "that", "it", "takes", "totalitarianism", "to", "an", "entirely", "new", "level", ",", "and", "besides", "all", "the", "control", "and", "the", "repression", ",", "there", "'s", "a", "classification", "system", "that", "is", "superimposed", "on", "the", "entire", "society", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 63, "question": "It is really, as John was saying there, totalitarianism gone crackers, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "is", "really", ",", "as", "John", "was", "saying", "there", ",", "totalitarianism", "gone", "crackers", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ",", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "VBG", "RB", ",", "NN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 64, "answer": "It is an unusual place.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "is", "an", "unusual", "place", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["John"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "WP", "NNP", "VBD", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 76, "question": "I mean, what should the American administration led by, say, John Kerry in South Korea, how should they be conducting themselves directly with the North Koreans would you say?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "what", "should", "the", "American", "administration", "led", "by", ",", "say", ",", "John", "Kerry", "in", "South", "Korea", ",", "how", "should", "they", "be", "conducting", "themselves", "directly", "with", "the", "North", "Koreans", "would", "you", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "MD", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "VBD", "IN", ",", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 77, "answer": "Well, I think, right now, I would agree with what Bob said earlier.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", ",", "right", "now", ",", "I", "would", "agree", "with", "what", "Bob", "said", "earlier", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["John Kerry"], "LOCATION": ["South Korea", "North Koreans"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 90, "question": "Is that true, as far as you're aware?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "true", ",", "as", "far", "as", "you", "'re", "aware", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", ",", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 91, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 130, "question": "How are you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 131, "answer": "Good.", "answer_tokens": ["Good", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 154, "question": "Why are you doing it and what do you hope to achieve?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "are", "you", "doing", "it", "and", "what", "do", "you", "hope", "to", "achieve", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", "CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 155, "answer": "It's gotten out of hand.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "gotten", "out", "of", "hand", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$50,000", "$100,000"]}, "docId": "130412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "$", "CD", "TO", "$", "CD", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 174, "question": "Do you know how much this is all going to cost you, too?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "how", "much", "this", "is", "all", "going", "to", "cost", "you", ",", "too", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "RB", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 175, "answer": "It could be from $50,000 to $100,000 a night, it looks like.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "could", "be", "from", "$", "50,000", "to", "$", "100,000", "a", "night", ",", "it", "looks", "like", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", ",", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 203, "question": "Free coffee as well?", "question_tokens": ["Free", "coffee", "as", "well", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 204, "answer": "Free coffee, as well.", "answer_tokens": ["Free", "coffee", ",", "as", "well", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 223, "question": "-- of America right now?", "question_tokens": ["--", "of", "America", "right", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "NNP", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 224, "answer": "I mean it's embarrassing.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", "it", "'s", "embarrassing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "''", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 229, "question": "What do you make of the dysfunction in Washington, where they can't seem to get any kind of budget deals done, any kind of economic plan sorted, nothing?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "make", "of", "the", "dysfunction", "in", "Washington", ",", "where", "they", "ca", "n't", "seem", "to", "get", "any", "kind", "of", "budget", "deals", "done", ",", "any", "kind", "of", "economic", "plan", "sorted", ",", "nothing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "VBN", ",", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 230, "answer": "Oh, they're -- they're out of their frickin' minds.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "they", "'re", "--", "they", "'re", "out", "of", "their", "frickin", "'", "minds", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Washington"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 238, "question": "Do you feel the gap between the rich and poor is just widening all the time now?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "feel", "the", "gap", "between", "the", "rich", "and", "poor", "is", "just", "widening", "all", "the", "time", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 239, "answer": "I think so.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 262, "question": "Can't we just talk about fun stuff, girls and lakes, summertime?", "question_tokens": ["Ca", "n't", "we", "just", "talk", "about", "fun", "stuff", ",", "girls", "and", "lakes", ",", "summertime", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "NN", ",", "NNS", "CC", "VBZ", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 263, "answer": "We can come to girls in a moment, don't you worry.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "can", "come", "to", "girls", "in", "a", "moment", ",", "do", "n't", "you", "worry", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", ",", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 274, "question": "How would you describe where you are politically now?", "question_tokens": ["How", "would", "you", "describe", "where", "you", "are", "politically", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 275, "answer": "I'm pretty confused, though.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "pretty", "confused", ",", "though", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", ":", "RB", "RB", ":", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "RB", "RBR", "."], "qSentId": 285, "question": "Why did you give up on Obama?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "did", "you", "give", "up", "on", "Obama", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 286, "answer": "Just the whole way things were going with -- especially just -- just separating the country even more.", "answer_tokens": ["Just", "the", "whole", "way", "things", "were", "going", "with", "--", "especially", "just", "--", "just", "separating", "the", "country", "even", "more", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "POS", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 288, "question": "But was that his fault?", "question_tokens": ["But", "was", "that", "his", "fault", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 289, "answer": "Someone's got to take the blame.", "answer_tokens": ["Someone", "'s", "got", "to", "take", "the", "blame", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 302, "question": "On the -- on the gay rights, gay marriage thing, are you from the -- you couldn't really give a damn category?", "question_tokens": ["On", "the", "--", "on", "the", "gay", "rights", ",", "gay", "marriage", "thing", ",", "are", "you", "from", "the", "--", "you", "could", "n't", "really", "give", "a", "damn", "category", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", ",", "NN", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", ":", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 303, "answer": "I don't care.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "care", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 323, "question": "It's very touchy, but I think at the end of the day, man, it's got to fall on the woman, you know?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "very", "touchy", ",", "but", "I", "think", "at", "the", "end", "of", "the", "day", ",", "man", ",", "it", "'s", "got", "to", "fall", "on", "the", "woman", ",", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 324, "answer": "Guns.", "answer_tokens": ["Guns", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "MD", "VB", ":", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 326, "question": "Are you in favor of any gun control?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "in", "favor", "of", "any", "gun", "control", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 327, "answer": "The only thing I could think of that might work -- no, I'm not for gun control.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "only", "thing", "I", "could", "think", "of", "that", "might", "work", "--", "no", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "for", "gun", "control", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 342, "question": "Do you own a lot of guns yourself?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "own", "a", "lot", "of", "guns", "yourself", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 343, "answer": "Yes, tons.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "tons", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 344, "question": "Would you consider yourself to be safe with them?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "consider", "yourself", "to", "be", "safe", "with", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 345, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 349, "question": "It's as simple as that?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "as", "simple", "as", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 350, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 351, "question": "So you think you need to have one for protection?", "question_tokens": ["So", "you", "think", "you", "need", "to", "have", "one", "for", "protection", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "CD", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 352, "answer": "I need to have one.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "need", "to", "have", "one", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 354, "question": "And you wouldn't hesitate to use it?", "question_tokens": ["And", "you", "would", "n't", "hesitate", "to", "use", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 355, "answer": "No, not at all.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "not", "at", "all", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 369, "question": "What if you're one of the families from Sandy Hook school?", "question_tokens": ["What", "if", "you", "'re", "one", "of", "the", "families", "from", "Sandy", "Hook", "school", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 370, "answer": "Well, I think there's families on both sides, from what I've read.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "there", "'s", "families", "on", "both", "sides", ",", "from", "what", "I", "'ve", "read", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Sandy Hook"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", "NNS", "VBP", ":", "NN", "IN", "IN", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "VB", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "CD", "NN", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 375, "question": "There's very little compromise, is there?", "question_tokens": ["There", "'s", "very", "little", "compromise", ",", "is", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 376, "answer": "Yes, and people are -- get so up in arms and get so hell bent one way or the other.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "and", "people", "are", "--", "get", "so", "up", "in", "arms", "and", "get", "so", "hell", "bent", "one", "way", "or", "the", "other", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 386, "question": "-- and Romney had lost?", "question_tokens": ["--", "and", "Romney", "had", "lost", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "CC", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 387, "answer": "That was fun.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "was", "fun", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}, "docId": "130412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "IN", "NNP", "DT", "NN", "WP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 388, "question": "Did he -- did he have a little joke at your expense?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "he", "--", "did", "he", "have", "a", "little", "joke", "at", "your", "expense", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 389, "answer": "He was -- I've always said this about Obama no matter what, he's cool.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "was", "--", "I", "'ve", "always", "said", "this", "about", "Obama", "no", "matter", "what", ",", "he", "'s", "cool", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "PRP", ",", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 394, "question": "What -- what did he say to you when he saw you again?", "question_tokens": ["What", "--", "what", "did", "he", "say", "to", "you", "when", "he", "saw", "you", "again", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", ":", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 395, "answer": "He probably said, you know, I think when I popped up in the receiving line, I was like -- he's like, Kid Rock, and I'm like, hey, man --", "answer_tokens": ["He", "probably", "said", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "think", "when", "I", "popped", "up", "in", "the", "receiving", "line", ",", "I", "was", "like", "--", "he", "'s", "like", ",", "Kid", "Rock", ",", "and", "I", "'m", "like", ",", "hey", ",", "man", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 415, "question": "What goes on in that moment?", "question_tokens": ["What", "goes", "on", "in", "that", "moment", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 416, "answer": "Because it came from Kid, it was expected.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "it", "came", "from", "Kid", ",", "it", "was", "expected", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VBN", "IN", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 425, "question": "A big gamble, though, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["A", "big", "gamble", ",", "though", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "JJ", ",", "IN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 426, "answer": "I will say we left that night -- I've had many of those dinners.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "will", "say", "we", "left", "that", "night", "--", "I", "'ve", "had", "many", "of", "those", "dinners", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Willie Nelson"]}, "docId": "130412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "WP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 455, "question": "You got some?", "question_tokens": ["You", "got", "some", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 456, "answer": "That's what Willie Nelson said.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "what", "Willie", "Nelson", "said", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ",", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 458, "question": "Good thing?", "question_tokens": ["Good", "thing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 459, "answer": "Legalize it, tax the hell out of it.", "answer_tokens": ["Legalize", "it", ",", "tax", "the", "hell", "out", "of", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 460, "question": "Simple as that?", "question_tokens": ["Simple", "as", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 461, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 474, "question": "How old is your boy now?", "question_tokens": ["How", "old", "is", "your", "boy", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 475, "answer": "Twenty.", "answer_tokens": ["Twenty", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 477, "question": "What did you say to him about drugs?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "say", "to", "him", "about", "drugs", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 478, "answer": "Careful.", "answer_tokens": ["Careful", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 479, "question": "Not, don't do it?", "question_tokens": ["Not", ",", "do", "n't", "do", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 480, "answer": "No, because remember that time I came home, fell down, I think it was Christmas Eve, slept on the bathroom floor.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "because", "remember", "that", "time", "I", "came", "home", ",", "fell", "down", ",", "I", "think", "it", "was", "Christmas", "Eve", ",", "slept", "on", "the", "bathroom", "floor", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 485, "question": "You're a living warning, basically?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "a", "living", "warning", ",", "basically", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBG", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 486, "answer": "Kind of, yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Kind", "of", ",", "yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Clint"]}, "docId": "130412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "RB", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 504, "question": "Is he a mate?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "he", "a", "mate", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 505, "answer": "I got to have dinner with Clint and just become, you know, I'd say a friend over the last few years.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "got", "to", "have", "dinner", "with", "Clint", "and", "just", "become", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "'d", "say", "a", "friend", "over", "the", "last", "few", "years", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "CD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 537, "question": "What made you write it?", "question_tokens": ["What", "made", "you", "write", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 538, "answer": "Well, I'd wrestled with perhaps doing a book one day.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'d", "wrestled", "with", "perhaps", "doing", "a", "book", "one", "day", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 552, "question": "That he wouldn't have liked you talking about him?", "question_tokens": ["That", "he", "would", "n't", "have", "liked", "you", "talking", "about", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 553, "answer": "No, not at all.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "not", "at", "all", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "PDT", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "DT", "DT", "NNS", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "."], "qSentId": 594, "question": "How did it come about?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "it", "come", "about", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 595, "answer": "Well, he had always teased me for all the years that I knew him, all the guys -- I was the youngest.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "he", "had", "always", "teased", "me", "for", "all", "the", "years", "that", "I", "knew", "him", ",", "all", "the", "guys", "--", "I", "was", "the", "youngest", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 645, "question": "Do you know?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 646, "answer": "You know, I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "JJS", "NNS", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 656, "question": "But it's a fortune, right?", "question_tokens": ["But", "it", "'s", "a", "fortune", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 657, "answer": "I would imagine to most people it's a fortune.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "imagine", "to", "most", "people", "it", "'s", "a", "fortune", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "VBZ", "RB", ",", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 704, "question": "The great moment of your life?", "question_tokens": ["The", "great", "moment", "of", "your", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 705, "answer": "Wow, that is so, so tough.", "answer_tokens": ["Wow", ",", "that", "is", "so", ",", "so", "tough", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bruno"]}, "docId": "130412pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "WP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "JJR", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 754, "question": "After the CNN show, lots of people call me, what can we do for you?", "question_tokens": ["After", "the", "CNN", "show", ",", "lots", "of", "people", "call", "me", ",", "what", "can", "we", "do", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 755, "answer": "But it was Bruno who wanted to do more to help families living in area motels.", "answer_tokens": ["But", "it", "was", "Bruno", "who", "wanted", "to", "do", "more", "to", "help", "families", "living", "in", "area", "motels", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]